[
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Are You Experienced\" was the debut album of which English-American rock band?",
    "choice1": "Motorhead",
    "choice2": "The Rolling Stones",
    "choice3": "Jimi Hendrix Experience",
    "choice4": "UFO",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Released in 1973, \"Seven Seas of Rhye\" was the breakthrough hit for which British rock band?",
    "choice1": "Fleetwood Mac",
    "choice2": "Queen",
    "choice3": "Black Sabbath",
    "choice4": "Deep Purple",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Nicknamed \"The Boss\", from which state does singer/songwriter \"Bruce Springsteen\" come from?",
    "choice1": "Florida",
    "choice2": "New York",
    "choice3": "Washington",
    "choice4": "New Jersey",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Scottish-born musician \"Ian Anderson\" was the lead vocalist for which band that disbanded in 2014?",
    "choice1": "King Crimson",
    "choice2": "Motorhead",
    "choice3": "Jethro Tull",
    "choice4": "The Moody Blues",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which classic rock band released the albums \"Houses of Holy\" and \"Physical Graffiti\"?",
    "choice1": "The Rolling Stones",
    "choice2": "Guns N' Roses",
    "choice3": "Def Leppard",
    "choice4": "Led Zeppelin",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which band reached #1 in the United States with the song \"Jump\" in 1984?",
    "choice1": "Van Halen",
    "choice2": "Extreme",
    "choice3": "Whitesnake",
    "choice4": "Rainbow",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Released in 1971, which rock band's first hit was \"Whiskey in the Jar\"?",
    "choice1": "ZZ Top",
    "choice2": "Status Quo",
    "choice3": "AC/DC",
    "choice4": "Thin Lizzy",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Formed in 1969, which rock band consisted of the members Stewart, Wood, McLagan, Jones and Lane?",
    "choice1": "Slade",
    "choice2": "The Faces",
    "choice3": "Wizard",
    "choice4": "The Rolling Stones",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Known for the hits \"No One Like You\" and \"Can't Live Without You,\" which German rock band was formed in 1965 by Rudolf Schenker?",
    "choice1": "Accept",
    "choice2": "Rammstein",
    "choice3": "The Scorpions",
    "choice4": "Helloween",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Which American rock band named their 1981 debut album \"Too Fast for Love\"?",
    "choice1": "Poison",
    "choice2": "Twisted Sister",
    "choice3": "Skid Row",
    "choice4": "Motley Crue",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "The songs \"Only You Can Rock Me\" and \"Arbory Hill\" appear on which UFO album?",
    "choice1": "UFO 2",
    "choice2": "Obsession",
    "choice3": "Lights Out",
    "choice4": "No Heavy Petting",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "Born in The Bronx, New York City, \"Joey Kramer\" is the drummer for which American rock band?",
    "choice1": "Aerosmith",
    "choice2": "Metallica",
    "choice3": "Cheap Trick",
    "choice4": "Creedence Clearwater Revival",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "In which US Rock trio is Frank Beard ironically the only member without a long beard?",
    "choice1": "Blackfoot",
    "choice2": "ZZ Top",
    "choice3": "Allman Brothers Band",
    "choice4": "Lynyrd Skynyrd",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "How many of AC/DC's singles have reached the UK Top 10?",
    "choice1": 0,
    "choice2": 1,
    "choice3": 2,
    "choice4": 3,
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "In what year did Iron Maiden release their classic album \"The Number of the Beast\"?",
    "choice1": 1982,
    "choice2": 1991,
    "choice3": 1979,
    "choice4": 1987,
    "answer": 1
  }
]